{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947086425046","data":{"timestamp":" 947086425045"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_183253"," gameId":" 4c23feba-5a79-4adc-a62c-74e1c4359377"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_dogo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" do"," userResponse":" do"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947086425576","data":{"timestamp":" 947086425576"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_183253"," gameId":" 4c23feba-5a79-4adc-a62c-74e1c4359377"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_dogo"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" go"," userResponse":" go"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947086429130","data":{"timestamp":" 947086429129"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_183253"," gameId":" 4c23feba-5a79-4adc-a62c-74e1c4359377"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mboga"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbo"," userResponse":" mbo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947086429576","data":{"timestamp":" 947086429576"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_183253"," gameId":" 4c23feba-5a79-4adc-a62c-74e1c4359377"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_mboga"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ga"," userResponse":" ga"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947086433971","data":{"timestamp":" 947086433971"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_183253"," gameId":" 4c23feba-5a79-4adc-a62c-74e1c4359377"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kombe"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ko"," userResponse":" ko"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947086434409","data":{"timestamp":" 947086434409"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_183253"," gameId":" 4c23feba-5a79-4adc-a62c-74e1c4359377"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_kombe"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbe"," userResponse":" mbe"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947086438679","data":{"timestamp":" 947086438679"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_183253"," gameId":" 4c23feba-5a79-4adc-a62c-74e1c4359377"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_panya"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pa"," userResponse":" pa"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947086439009","data":{"timestamp":" 947086439009"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_183253"," gameId":" 4c23feba-5a79-4adc-a62c-74e1c4359377"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_panya"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nya"," userResponse":" nya"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947086448205","data":{"timestamp":" 947086448204"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_183253"," gameId":" 4c23feba-5a79-4adc-a62c-74e1c4359377"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_njaa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" nja"," userResponse":" nja"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947086449326","data":{"timestamp":" 947086449325"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_183253"," gameId":" 4c23feba-5a79-4adc-a62c-74e1c4359377"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_njaa"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947086452922","data":{"timestamp":" 947086452922"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_183253"," gameId":" 4c23feba-5a79-4adc-a62c-74e1c4359377"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pua"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" pu"," userResponse":" pu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947086453510","data":{"timestamp":" 947086453510"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_183253"," gameId":" 4c23feba-5a79-4adc-a62c-74e1c4359377"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_pua"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" a"," userResponse":" a"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947086456866","data":{"timestamp":" 947086456866"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_183253"," gameId":" 4c23feba-5a79-4adc-a62c-74e1c4359377"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_radhi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ra"," userResponse":" ra"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947086457346","data":{"timestamp":" 947086457346"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_183253"," gameId":" 4c23feba-5a79-4adc-a62c-74e1c4359377"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_radhi"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" dhi"," userResponse":" dhi"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947086460527","data":{"timestamp":" 947086460527"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_183253"," gameId":" 4c23feba-5a79-4adc-a62c-74e1c4359377"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_nguo"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" ngu"," userResponse":" ngu"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947086461598","data":{"timestamp":" 947086461598"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_183253"," gameId":" 4c23feba-5a79-4adc-a62c-74e1c4359377"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_nguo"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" o"," userResponse":" o"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947086464854","data":{"timestamp":" 947086464853"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_183253"," gameId":" 4c23feba-5a79-4adc-a62c-74e1c4359377"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_meza"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" me"," userResponse":" me"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947086465376","data":{"timestamp":" 947086465376"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_183253"," gameId":" 4c23feba-5a79-4adc-a62c-74e1c4359377"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_meza"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" za"," userResponse":" za"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947086471519","data":{"timestamp":" 947086471519"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_183253"," gameId":" 4c23feba-5a79-4adc-a62c-74e1c4359377"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_chombo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" cho"," userResponse":" cho"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947086472157","data":{"timestamp":" 947086472157"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_183253"," gameId":" 4c23feba-5a79-4adc-a62c-74e1c4359377"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" Spell word"," problemName":" write_chombo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 2"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" mbo"," userResponse":" mbo"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"spelling:datasource_2__it_2","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947086474019","data":{"timestamp":" 947086474018"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_183253"," gameId":" 4c23feba-5a79-4adc-a62c-74e1c4359377"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" ENDTUTOR"," problemName":" write_chombo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947086481329","data":{"timestamp":" 947086481328"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_183253"," gameId":" 4c23feba-5a79-4adc-a62c-74e1c4359377"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" spelling"," tutorId":" spelling_datasource_2__it_2"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" spell_2"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" write_chombo"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947086492480","data":{"timestamp":" 947086492480"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_183253"," gameId":" 8d65a85f-5432-44a6-ba80-d0c773206608"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninampenda mwalimu wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAMPENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.echo::story_8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947086493994","data":{"timestamp":" 947086493994"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_183253"," gameId":" 8d65a85f-5432-44a6-ba80-d0c773206608"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" WORD"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" Ninampenda mwalimu wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"activity_selector","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"947086494065","data":{"timestamp":" 947086494065"," userId":" 5B12002947"," sessionId":" 5B12002947_20000105_183253"," gameId":" 8d65a85f-5432-44a6-ba80-d0c773206608"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" story_reading"," tutorId":" story.echo__story_8"," matrixName":" literacy"," levelName":" END"," taskName":" story"," problemName":" Ninampenda mwalimu wangu."," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" 0"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" NINAMPENDA"," userResponse":" TOUCH_GENERATED"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}